{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Humidifier Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40303/":{"taskOID":40303,"originalTaskOID":40303,"setID":603,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":4803,"questionDisplayText":"Service Need(s)","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need service? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":717,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Air is drier than it should be","answerDisplayText":"Air is drier than it should be","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":718,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Air is more moist than it should be","answerDisplayText":"Air is more moist than it should be","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5551,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"See/smell mold, mildew","answerDisplayText":"See/smell mold, mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3106,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Humidifier not getting water","answerDisplayText":"Humidifier not getting water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3107,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Humidifier using too much  water","answerDisplayText":"Humidifier using too much  water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6961,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wick/sponge pad is clogged or soldified","answerDisplayText":"Wick/sponge pad is clogged or soldified","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3815,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Metal grill caked with mineral deposits","answerDisplayText":"Metal grill caked with mineral deposits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6795,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Want to add air purifier","answerDisplayText":"Want to add air purifier","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6799,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want to add humistat","answerDisplayText":"Want to add humistat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6817,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Want to replace","answerDisplayText":"Want to replace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6601,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Unit needs cleaning/checking","answerDisplayText":"Unit needs cleaning/checking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":4803,"questionDisplayText":"Service Need(s)","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Why do you need service? (Check all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":717,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Air is drier than it should be","answerDisplayText":"Air is drier than it should be","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":718,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Air is more moist than it should be","answerDisplayText":"Air is more moist than it should be","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5551,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"See/smell mold, mildew","answerDisplayText":"See/smell mold, mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3106,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Humidifier not getting water","answerDisplayText":"Humidifier not getting water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3107,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Humidifier using too much  water","answerDisplayText":"Humidifier using too much  water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6961,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wick/sponge pad is clogged or soldified","answerDisplayText":"Wick/sponge pad is clogged or soldified","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3815,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Metal grill caked with mineral deposits","answerDisplayText":"Metal grill caked with mineral deposits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6795,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Want to add air purifier","answerDisplayText":"Want to add air purifier","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6799,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want to add humistat","answerDisplayText":"Want to add humistat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6817,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Want to replace","answerDisplayText":"Want to replace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6601,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Unit needs cleaning/checking","answerDisplayText":"Unit needs cleaning/checking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":717,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Air is drier than it should be","answerDisplayText":"Air is drier than it should be","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":718,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Air is more moist than it should be","answerDisplayText":"Air is more moist than it should be","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5551,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"See/smell mold, mildew","answerDisplayText":"See/smell mold, mildew","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3106,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Humidifier not getting water","answerDisplayText":"Humidifier not getting water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3107,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Humidifier using too much  water","answerDisplayText":"Humidifier using too much  water","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6961,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wick/sponge pad is clogged or soldified","answerDisplayText":"Wick/sponge pad is clogged or soldified","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3815,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Metal grill caked with mineral deposits","answerDisplayText":"Metal grill caked with mineral deposits","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6795,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Want to add air purifier","answerDisplayText":"Want to add air purifier","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6799,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Want to add humistat","answerDisplayText":"Want to add humistat","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6817,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Want to replace","answerDisplayText":"Want to replace","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6601,"answerDisplaySequence":11,"answerText":"Unit needs cleaning/checking","answerDisplayText":"Unit needs cleaning/checking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":12,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":7735,"questionDisplayText":"What kind of location is this?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"What kind of location is this?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":20767,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Home/Residence","answerDisplayText":"Home/Residence","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":20766,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Business","answerDisplayText":"Business","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":7,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/40303/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40303,"taskName":"Central Humidifier - Repair or Service","taskDescription":"Repair or Service a Central Humidifier","xmTaskDescriptor":"Humidifier Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":135,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"Humidifier conditioning coolers","textMessagingName":"Repair Humidifier","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes the sponge wheel \u0026 the sprayer types. Used to raise humidity, especially during the winter to offset extreme dryness caused by the most popular heating systems. Benefits include eliminating dry-mouth, increased comfort \u0026 reduced static electricity. Breakdowns are common if not properly maintained.","rolloverShortDesc":"Attaches to furnace to moisten the air.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair or Service a Central Humidifier.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Humidifier Repair \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Fix Whole House Humidifier","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":39,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Central Humidifier Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Central Humidifier - Repair or Service","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Central Humidifier Project","urlName":"Central-Humidifier-Repair-or-Service","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":false,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Humidifier Repair Services - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | HomeAdvisor","searchKeywords":"Airconditioning,Central,Humidifier,conditioning,coolers,systems,heating,units,whole,room,hvac,furnace,cooling,airconditioners,air,system,ac","emcCategoryOid":-12002,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":603,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false}}